HEY WELCOME TO THE END OF THE COURSE.
嘿，欢迎来到课程结束。
YOU MADE IT.
你做到了。
YOU DID IT.
恭喜你。
You should be proud that you were able to stick with the entire course.
您应该为能够坚持整个课程而感到自豪。
I realize it's very long.
我意识到它很长。
Certainly and parts may maybe a little dry so I'm very pleased that you got through the course.
当然，零件可能有点干，所以我很高兴你通过了课程。
And I want to just thank you for taking the time to do it and I honestly hope that it was useful to
我只想感谢您抽出时间来做这件事，我真诚地希望它对您有用
you.
你。
I hope this course has been valuable and I hope it's something that you're glad that you did.
我希望这门课程很有价值，我希望你很高兴你这样做了。
I really spent a lot of time and a lot of energy and put in a lot of thought and I hope that you were
我真的花了很多时间和精力，想了很多，我希望你是
able to feel that as you went through this course I have actually been working on this course for years.
能够感觉到，当您完成这门课程时，我实际上已经在这门课程上工作了多年。
So again genuinely great job and thank you very much.
所以再次真正伟大的工作，非常感谢你。
And I want to just go over a couple of things a couple of recommendations I have things I hope you can
我想谈谈一些事情一些建议我有一些事情希望你能
keep in mind for how to improve your your English abilities going forward things to keep in mind in
记住如何提高你的英语能力
your English learning journey.
你的英语学习之旅。
Number one is the importance of review as you were going through the course.
第一个是复习的重要性，因为你正在学习这门课程。
I hope that you took the time to take notes.
我希望你花时间做笔记。
I hope that you took the time to seriously consider each each lesson and that you didn't just rush through
我希望你花时间认真考虑每一节课，而不是匆忙完成
it.
它。
Now if you did that it's very important to review to keep all of those things fresh.
现在，如果您这样做了，那么复习以保持所有这些内容的新鲜度非常重要。
If you just go through something once it can easily fade away so try to review the notes that you took.
如果你只是经历了一些事情，它很容易消失，所以试着回顾你做的笔记。 如果需要，不要害怕实际回去观看特定的课程。
In fact you might take a break and go through the entire course again if you're really really crazy.
事实上，如果你真的很疯狂，你可能会休息一下并重新完成整个课程。
I do that when I read a book I usually go back and read the whole book again.
当我读一本书时，我会这样做，我通常会回去再读一遍整本书。
Why.
为什么。
Because I want to make sure I didn't miss anything that maybe I didn't catch the first time through.
因为我想确保我没有错过任何可能我第一次没有抓住的东西。
So don't be afraid to do that if you enjoyed the course.
因此，如果您喜欢这门课程，请不要害怕这样做。
It might be valuable to you to go back and actually go through the course again review your notes from
回过头来重新学习课程可能对您很有价值，并复习您的笔记 不时。
And most importantly most importantly try to use the stuff that you learned in this course in your daily
最重要的是尝试在日常生活中使用您在本课程中学到的东西
life.
生活。
I hope that everything you learn in this course is actually useful in real life.
我希望您在本课程中学到的所有内容都对现实生活有用。
I was very careful to make sure all of the phrases and the different words we learned and all of the
我非常小心地确保我们学到的所有短语和不同的单词以及所有的
different skills that we learned in this course can actually be used in real life.
我们在本课程中学到的不同技能实际上可以在现实生活中使用。
So I hope that you start using them because if you start using them in your conversations and situations
所以我希望你开始使用它们，因为如果你开始在你的对话和情境中使用它们
that you encounter then you're going to remember more clearly all of those things and it's going to
你遇到然后你会更清楚地记住所有这些事情
become part of your ability to communicate.
成为你沟通能力的一部分。
So again review Don't be afraid to go back and re watch and certainly start using everything that you
所以再次回顾不要害怕回去重新观看，当然要开始使用你的一切
learned as much as possible in your daily life.
在日常生活中尽可能多地学习。
Number two is extremely important.
第二个非常重要。
And I mentioned it a lot and it's the reason why I always recommend that you record yourself when you're
我经常提到它，这就是为什么我总是建议你在
speaking if you don't have others to practice with because awareness is really the key to moving forward
如果你没有其他人可以练习，那就说吧，因为意识真的是前进的关键
and building better habits.
并建立更好的习惯。
I'll say it a thousand times if I need to.
如果需要，我会说一千遍。
It is the key to success.
这是成功的关键。
If you don't know what you're saying and you're not aware of what you're saying then you're really never
如果你不知道自己在说什么，也不知道自己在说什么，那么你真的永远不会
going to sound more fluent.
听起来更流利。
Now you might use the new words and phrases.
现在你可以使用新的单词和短语了。
That's great.
那太棒了。
And you're you're going to be able to handle more situations.
And you're you're goi 而你就是你ng 能够处理更多的情况。
That's wonderful.
那好极了。
But you really need to develop a keen awareness of what is coming out of your own mouth in order to
但是你真的需要对从你自己嘴里说出来的东西产生敏锐的意识，以便
become more fluent and to use the things that you learned in this course.
变得更加流利并使用您在本课程中学到的东西。
Well and properly to actually take the next step.
好，正确地实际采取下一步。
Awareness is key.
意识是关键。
So do the exercises that we practiced in this course and also redo some of the things that are attached
所以做我们在本课程中练习的练习，并重做一些附带的东西
to each lesson in the in the review part by practicing on a daily basis by giving yourself little tasks
通过每天给自己一些小任务来练习复习部分中的每节课
and recording those tasks and then listening to them again.
并记录这些任务，然后再听一遍。
You're going to become more aware of what you say when you speak.
当你说话时，你会更加意识到你在说什么。
You're going to be able to hear yourself better and the more you do that the better your habits will
您将能够更好地听到自己的声音，并且做得越多，您的习惯就会越好
be the stronger your good habits will be and the faster you'll be able to correct or to fix your bad
你的好习惯越强，你就能越快纠正或改正你的坏习惯
habits.
习惯。
So I hope that you continue to practice and I hope that you continue to record that practice so that
所以我希望你继续练习，我希望你继续记录练习，以便
you can build that awareness so that you can then develop proper habits and get rid of the habits that
你可以建立这种意识，这样你就可以养成适当的习惯并摆脱那些
you don't like about your spoken English.
你不喜欢你的英语口语。
Finally I would encourage you if you're working on other aspects of your spoken English for example
最后，如果您正在研究英语口语的其他方面，我会鼓励您
pronunciation or how to think in English and other things.
发音或如何用英语和其他东西思考。
I would encourage you to check out my other courses because they're really meant to focus on specific
我鼓励你查看我的其他课程，因为它们真的是为了专注于特定的
areas of spoken English to help you improve in other ways.
英语口语领域，以帮助您在其他方面提高。
In addition to this worse those things can help you build out those good speaking habits.
除了这个更糟糕的事情之外，这些事情还可以帮助你养成良好的说话习惯。
I want to wish you the best of luck in your English language journey in the future and I hope to see
我想祝你在未来的英语之旅中好运，我希望看到
you in another course.
你在另一门课。